<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Home on Alex Greig</title>
    <link>https://alexgreig.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Home on Alex Greig</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://alexgreig.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>China&#39;s &#34;Uninvestability&#34; Causing Attractive Investment Opportunity</title>
      <link>https://alexgreig.com/posts/china-uninvestability/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexgreig.com/posts/china-uninvestability/</guid>
      
      <description>Thesis China&amp;rsquo;s market has become dislocated as investors retract capital due to fears of regulation in light of the US, China tensions. This presents an opportunity to buy undervalued, quality businesses with strengthing fundamentals and cashflow growth; with earnings season presenting a catalyst for investor reevaluation of the market. In addition, more favourable policy surrounding stimulus measures will aid investor confidence in the market&amp;rsquo;s stablisation and will actualise a deleveraging of businesses to a more robust state.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Useful Markdown Functions</title>
      <link>https://alexgreig.com/posts/template/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Feb 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexgreig.com/posts/template/</guid>
      
      <description>Paragraph Xerum, quo qui aut unt expliquam qui dolut labo. Aque venitatiusda cum, voluptionse latur sitiae dolessi aut parist aut dollo enim qui voluptate ma dolestendit peritin re plis aut quas inctum laceat est volestemque commosa as cus endigna tectur, offic to cor sequas etum rerum idem sintibus eiur? Quianimin porecus evelectur, cum que nis nust voloribus ratem aut omnimi, sitatur? Quiatem. Nam, omnis sum am facea corem alique molestrunt et eos evelece arcillit ut aut eos eos nus, sin conecerem erum fuga.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://alexgreig.com/pages/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://alexgreig.com/pages/about/</guid>
      
      <description>Alex is a highly driven individual with a desire to succeed in all areas. High attention to detail and ability to make quick, effective decisions. Able to discern complex concepts and apply new knowledge to solve problems and achieve requested outcomes. Experienced with equity derivatives, their modeling and risk management. In addition, Alex has performed extensive market analysis and backtesting, using python as the primary language of choice.
Some projects that I have created personally are below:</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
